Hello everyone! This is Hitomi Takamoto from Equal Love!
So, this is the Equal Love Boat Racing Club!
Today, we are here! We are here at Toda Boat Race!
I've visited Tamagawa, Edogawa, and Fukuoka before, but today is my first time in Saitama Prefecture!
Today is my first visit to Saitama Prefecture!
I'm here at Toda Auto Race! Wow! Thank you very much!
And to my surprise, Director Hashihara is not here today...
But today, we have a new member, this girl!
Hi!
Hello!
Hello! I'm Shoko Takioki!
Yay! Shoko is here!
I'm so happy!
Yay! I've been wanting to try it too.
I haven't done it yet.
I haven't!
So today, I'm a Shoko person.
Shoko people.
I'm going to enjoy moto racing with you!
Yay!
Let's start with the entrance today!
Let's go go go go!
Let's go, go, go, go!
Oh! That's right! Before we go in, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
I was wondering about something we saw earlier.
You can see it here...
Boat Race Toda!
Oh, look!
There's a real boat sparkling!
It's amazing!
It's all decorated!
Can I ride it?
What? You want to go on it?
Can I?
Then this is the real thing!
It's real!
Are you sure?
Wait, wait, wait! For the first time in my life, I'm going on a boat!
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
You're a real gal, gal!
That's great!
But it's supposed to be like this, right?
What? Sitting on your back?
Yeah, that's what you say.
Oh, my God! There's nothing to protect you.
Oh, my God. Look at this.
A real gal! A real gal!
It's real!
Wow! It's a gyaru-tei.
It's Gal.
I'm so happy!
Something great just happened!
That's great!
We're off to a good start.
I feel like I'm going to win today.
Let's do it.
Well, I'm sorry, I'm a little pressed for time.
We'll get you in as soon as we can.
Okay.
It's raining.
It really is.Really.
It's raining super-jumbo and unbelievable!
It's really raining.
It's raining.
We'll let you in through the gate.
How do we enter?
Yes, after you put in 100 yen.
You can enter the boat race track on your trip.
Yay!
Let's put in 100 yen.
Here we go.
Oh, I put it in!
I'm in!
I put it in.
All right.
Okay, let's get on with it.
Let's get on with it.
We're going to start off a little slow today.
I'll be with Chao.
I'll send you on your way.
I'm so happy for you!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
I've been thinking about you for a long time.
Really?
Oh, I can already hear the engines.
It's starting, race four. The sound of the rain.
The sound of the rain, and the whirring, and the humming, and the...
Wow, wow, wow.
Wait, I thought I said one, two, five...
Wait, I've never been down this close before.
It's raining like crazy, by the way.
By the way, it's raining like crazy.
The moment they get home, it's live.
I'll be able to see it.
One, one, one, one, five.
Wait, wait, wait. That's not fair.
I should've bought this.
I should've bought this. Second place is so tight.
No, but here at the end, second place, second place, second place, second place, second place...
I should've bought it. I should've bought it.
I won, but I should've bought it.
We were just predicting...
I predicted it and it came true. But I didn't buy it.
So we went inside the building.
What a surprise!
Yay!
I'll start with the rice.
Thank you. I don't know if this is such a luxury.
I'm so happy.
We're hungry for food, aren't we?
So let's eat the rice for the game!
Yay! This is great!
I want to win, so I'm going to win?
I wonder if I'll win.
I'm going to go to a ramen shop.
Okay, let's eat what we want to eat.
Okay, bye-bye until next time.
Let's choose what we want to eat!
So here's what we ordered!
First of all, we both ordered the same thing!
It looks like some kind of specialty!It looks like some kind of specialty.
It's just an oil chair.
Mini... this is a mini!
Yes, I got a mini one, but it's quite a big one!
And here it is!
It's called "togamanchi"!
And this is the pork cutlet with sauce!
I knew I had to start with the cutlet.
I have to win, don't I?
So I'll try it as soon as possible!
Bon appétit!
It looks so delicious, I don't know what to do!
Wow, right... it's so fluffy!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wow!
Bon appétit!
What are we going to do? What are you going to do with it?
Go ahead!
Oh, it looks so good!
Is it good?
It's tender and has a thick demi.
It's demi, right? I thought it was ketchup, but I didn't expect demi.
Too good, I can't wait for you to try it!
I can't imagine a boat racing track with such a delicious demi-crusted visual.
Surely, it's a boat race track, right?
For a moment I forget, eh, wait, it looks so delicious.
It's not good?
Oh my God!
It's so good!
If a restaurant like this were to open in Harajuku, there would be a huge line!
Want some of this?
Sauce cutlet.
Do you think this will win?
You can win.
Do you think we can win today?
It's a sauced pork cutlet.
Let's win for sure.
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum!
Let's buy some and go home. I'm sure we'll win.
We'll win no matter what. It's important to have the right mindset.
I'll learn from you. You're the first to say it's all about the spirit.
Finally, a bite of the menchikatsu. Toda Menchikatsu is famous, isn't it?
Toda Menchis are famous.
It's famous. -Thank you.
So good!
I don't want to go home a loser.
I don't want to go home after losing I'll pay the 100 yen drink fee and have a nice meal at the food court
That's one way to have fun.
Listen, I don't want to lose today.
I've been winning a lot in my private life lately. The last one was the Boat Race All Star in May.
And after that, there was a big event called Flimrose. I won both the SG and the G1 championship.
I won both! That's amazing! God! I won! I won, and I'm back!
The reason why I was able to win is because a lot of boat racing fans commented in the comment section of the Fukuoka Boat Race Club.
They commented a lot!
It makes me stronger! Thank you all!
I'm so happy to see that even boat race fans who are not fans of Ikola are commenting on my blog, so the power of your comments is great.
I'd like to thank you all for your comments, and I hope you'll comment again today on something that may not be relevant today, but I'm sure you'll enjoy the boat race.
I'd be very happy if you could comment again on the boat race.
I'm new to boat racing, but I studied really hard.
I studied like I took an entrance exam for a year. I've got the important stuff down, but it was a little difficult.I studied like I took an entrance exam for a year. I've got the important parts down, but it was a little difficult.
I've been studying the trends in Toda today, and the width of the water surface at Boat Race Toda is very narrow, so the first mark is at a slight angle.
So the first mark is at a slight angle, so it's difficult for the first boat to go around.
The first course has the worst percentage of first place finishes because it's easy for other boats to come.
I've got information that the first boat has a hard time coming in, so the third and fourth boats tend to come in first place.
Then that's our target.
Proof! Like my 13.
Proof!
Yes!
It's possible!
Yes! I'm so glad it's possible.
Connect the two or three in a row with the No. 4.
Yeah, I think I'm going to go with #4.
Oh, come on.
Don't win more than me.
I'm gonna win!
It's a weapon. I knew it. It's a team game.
Thank you! That's great!
But I might run out again.
But you never know, you never know, you might win.
Oh, yeah?
Just a step in the right direction.
Oh, I'm so glad! You know, I've been trying to get people to join our club.
No one's been inducted yet.
You mean, like, the candidates just keep coming in?
I'm just saying, if I get good grades, maybe I'll join the club.
Maybe.
That's how much I'm betting on it.
I'm so excited!
I'll do my best!
Okay, so, there you have it!
Thank you for the food!
Finished!
Now that you're full...
Then the race!
I'd like to go...
But today's race is still...
No!
I'm going to do something that you can't predict.
I'm going to do something today that you can't predict!
What?
So we're gonna get ready, and then we're gonna...
Let's go!
Wait for me!
So, I changed my clothes!
Ta-da!
I'm wearing a special Shogun's uniform today!
Thank you very much!
The general's uniform is yellow, the yellow of the member's color, the yellow of the No.2 boat!
It suits me so well!
I'm wearing the red color of the third boat, because my member color is red!
It's so awesome!
Oh my gosh!
It's amazing! It's my dream! My dream came true!
Look at this! What a surprise!
I'm going to experience Boat Race VR Splash Battle!
It looks so difficult!
It's really a game where you can experience boat racing in VR on this thing.
There seems to be a tutorial, so I'll start from there!
You have to turn the boat all the way to the left by yourself, and when it's all the way around, you have to fix it.You have to turn it all the way to the left by yourself, and when it's all the way around, you have to fix it.
Those are the only two things I have to do, but the rest is just getting used to it!
Amazing!
Do you want me to stop behind you? Are you okay?
I'll explain now!
Turn the handle to the right and left to turn, and the plane splat line will be launched!
Wow! Isn't it scary?
It's amazing! It's so scary!
Next, choose a character!
You're on your phone! Boat racing is dark!
It's scary! I'm scared!
Shall we begin?
Is it starting?
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Ah! Is that it?
Now, automatic! Automatic!
Go! Now! Now! Now! Now! Now! Now! Now! Now! Now!
Now! Now! Now! Now! Now!
The wind is blowing!
Oh, I can't open it!
Oh, it won't open!
Why, why, why!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
No! No!
Aah!
Go!
Go around!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go!
Around!
Okay, we're good.
I'm gonna recart!
Oh, wait, that's so crazy.
Boo boo!
What's the number on this one?
I'm in the Rock, and I'm about 30 seconds behind you!
I'm down too safe, and one of the other ones is too good, and I'm screwed, but it's like I'm doing it like a boat racer, and I'm having so much fun.
I'm having so much fun, it's like being a boat racer!
We'll do a second example, and then you can show us how the good ones do it.
Well, I'd like to see it.
Kiraguri's.
One of the two,
Wait a minute, this is getting a little difficult.
I want to get into it, this. I want this in my house.
How can I improve on my earlier race?
Well, first of all, do this. Lean forward.
I didn't do this once before.
I was already turning with just the handlebars.
Like this! Like this!
Monkey turn.
Like this.
And when it turns, put it back.
I think I can do it!
I'd like to compete with Shoko.
Shoko was nowhere to be foundShoko was nowhere to be found.
I was a long way off too, but she was further back.
Well, then, the second round, the last, right?
I'll do my best.
Okay, good.
Okay, let's go for it.
Here we go.
Let's go.
I don't know.
Oh, no.
Go!
No, I can't turn.
No, you hit me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Why, why, why, why, why
Number one.
Go!
Go, go, go, go, go
Go! No!
Bump, bump
Go, go, go, go!
Onward, onward, onward!
forward, forward, forward, forward!
יצу, kane🐷
χзу
yes owning
Ã insan
oh
ah
ah ah ah ah ah
shopping
Throw!
No!
Whoo!
So, what do you think?
Huh!
Huh! That was too fast!
Oh, shit!
Huh!
Oh, we lost?
Whoo!
Chance!
Whoo! He threw it!
Take a chance!
Chance!
Ha-ha-ha!
Okay, what's the verdict?
What's the verdict?
What? What? I came in third! That's great!
I'm so happy! I'm, what? Huh? What? If I hadn't gotten stuck at the last mark, I would have been first?
I came in first? That's awesome! I want to do it again!
I got first place in the footsies with one hand on the steering wheel.
Yes, that was faster. That was definitely faster.
But he did it! He did it!But you know what? He did it! I did it!
This was so much fun! I'm so frustrated! I'm so frustrated!
But it was so much fun! It was awesome! It was so much fun! Great!
So, the Sports Racing VR Splash Battle experience is over! I'm done!
I'm so sweaty! It's awesome! But it's hot! So hot!
My throat is killing me! I screamed! I screamed!
It was so much fun! So much fun!
This is really the most fun I've had in a while! But we didn't win first place anymore!
We wanted to get revenge again, but the staff of Sports Race Strada is now offering to give a lecture directly to the athletes if we get a chance someday! I was thinking that I would like to come back again.
I'd like to end today on a high note, hoping that they will be able to do it again and come back!
And what else, you did a great job! You did your best, didn't you?
Wow! I'll take it! Thank you!
What? You did great, didn't you? What?
What? You're so cute!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! What's this? Is that an Aqukey? It's an Aqukey!
Oh, my God! I love it! Wait, wait, wait!
Where is it? That's mine!
What? ! That's mine!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Wait a minute!
You're a candidate? What? Sir? Sir!
Thank you! Oh, my God! Neck strumpet!
It's so cute!
I think I'll wear it next time and ask you to teach me!
We will definitely come back to Boat Race Toda! We will!
Awesome!!! Thank you! Bon appétit!
Yes! So, that's it for today, we've already got a lot of video,
Next time! I'm going to try to win with Mr. Toda as the second part!
I'll do my best!
So, thank you very much for watching today!
So, bye-bye!